Guide to the Thomas M. Disch Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- September 2006 Acquisition, 1908-2007; 52; (66 boxes) + 1 art
  - Drawings and paintings, undated
  - Album of paintings, undated
  - Thomas Disch photograph, (photocopy), undated
  - Black and white photograph of people, undated
  - Crossword puzzle, laminated, undated
  - "The Squirrel Cage," musical score based on a story by Thomas Disch, undated
  - Notebook, 1978-1982 (Box 104 (Oversize))
  - Photograph album, undated (Box 105 (Oversize))
  - Scrapbook of news clippings, 1959-1962 (Box 106 (Oversize))
  - "Ben Hur," posters, 1989 (Box 107 (Oversize))
  - Audiovisual Material
    Boxes 108-109 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Tapes of radio interviews, from: Box 57
      - In Different Voices: T. S. Eliot at 100, Symphony Space, radio program", 1988 October 22; 1; 01:34:53; The program is distorted at times. (Box 108, Item barcode 39002091399239)
      - Alexander, Jane, undated; 1; 01:34:13; There is high background noise on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 108, Item barcode 39002091399221)
      - Letter from New York, undated; 1; 00:35:18 (Box 108, Item barcode 39002091399247)
      - Strieber tape, undated; 1; 00:02:00; The program is distorted at times. (Box 108, Item barcode 39002091399262)
        Author Whitley Strieber is recorded leaving a message on an answering machine regarding his book "Communion" from 00:54 until 01:53.
      - "Public Affairs #16", undated; 1; 00:29:24 (Box 108, Item barcode 39002091399254)
      - Aenouera [J. H.], undated; 1; 01:16:22 (Box 108, Item barcode 39002091399213)
    - "Byway Musical--The Run Through, books and lyrics--Tom Disch, music--Gerald Ginsberg, demonstration tape", undated; 1; 00:20:35; The program runs 11 minutes and repeats. The first version contains tone to match audio with projector slides. (Box 109, Item barcode 39002091398819)
  - Computer media
    Boxes 110-113 (computer and computer disks): Restricted Fragile Material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Computer, undated (Box 113)
      2006-ycal-0921-2585-0105
      Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - CARDINAL DETOXES, 2006-ycal-2585-0001; 1 (Box 110)
    - POETRY BIBLIOG, 2006-ycal-2585-0002; 1 (Box 110)
    - [no label information], 2006-ycal-2585-0003; 1 (Box 110)
    - [no label information], 2006-ycal-2585-0004; 1 (Box 110)
    - FULL GREEN LANTERN King of the Kalahari 21st of June Reviews, 2006-ycal-2585-0005; 1 (Box 110)
    - GLASNOST BEN HUR FULL, 2006-ycal-2585-0006; 1 (Box 110)
    - BEN HUR #2, 2006-ycal-2585-0007; 1 (Box 110)
    - BEN HUR #3, 2006-ycal-2585-0008; 1 (Box 110)
    - BWAY MUSICAL/RUN-THRU VAMPIRES early notes JOYCELIN SHRAGER CARDINAL, 2006-ycal-2585-0009; 1 (Box 110)
    - SHADOW GOV KOCH BWAY LIARS/VIDEO D ONE NIGHTS/AUSSIES, 2006-ycal-2585-0010; 1 (Box 110)
    - THEATER 54 (Oct '90+), 2006-ycal-2585-0011; 1 (Box 110)
    - KRONIC ARG DESSERTS EARTH INVADED OUR COMB TIME VINE HEMLOCK, 2006-ycal-2585-0012; 1 (Box 110)
    - JOHNS HOPKINS, 2006-ycal-2585-0013; 1 (Box 110)
    - MIAMI VICE TIME TRAVEL Getting into Death, 2006-ycal-2585-0014; 1 (Box 110)
    - LETTERS 6 Feb 1989-- FULL, 2006-ycal-2585-0015; 1 (Box 110)
    - DIARY 6 APRIL 1990+ copied, 2006-ycal-2585-0016; 1 (Box 110)
    - DIARY 4 SEPT '86 to JULY 13 '88 COPIED FULL, 2006-ycal-2585-0017; 1 (Box 110)
    - VAMPIRES SCRIPT SCI.REV-1-9, 2006-ycal-2585-0018; 1 (Box 110)
    - VAMPIRES ACT 2, 2006-ycal-2585-0019; 1 (Box 110)
    - VAMPIRES #3, 2006-ycal-2585-0020; 1 (Box 110)
    - TEACUP SANTA/DISNEY TURNIP FULL, 2006-ycal-2585-0021; 1 (Box 110)
    - POEMS SUMMER '85 thru summer '86 FULL, 2006-ycal-2585-0022; 1 (Box 110)
    - POEMS AUG 89+, 2006-ycal-2585-0023; 1 (Box 110)
    - POEMS SEPT '86-- AUG '89, 2006-ycal-2585-0024; 1 (Box 110)
    - Teddy Bears in Hell NAKED LADY, 2006-ycal-2585-0025; 1 (Box 110)
    - The Priest D, 2006-ycal-2585-0026; 1 (Box 110)
    - 1 WORK AUTOMOBILE ONTOGONY, 2006-ycal-2585-0027; 1 (Box 110)
    - ROYAL WEDDING 7 WONDERS WORK 1 + 2 FULL 42K left, 2006-ycal-2585-0028; 1 (Box 110)
    - FF, 2006-ycal-2585-0029; 1 (Box 110)
    - WOMEN OF BOGAZKOY, 2006-ycal-2585-0030; 1 (Box 110)
    - COGNETICS SOFTWARE Amnesia Demo 5/31/84, 2006-ycal-2585-0031; 1 (Box 110)
    - NBCC Aug '89+ THRU JAN 13 '91 FULL, 2006-ycal-2585-0032; 1 (Box 110)
    - BLURBS/JOHNS H SF BIBLIO-CATALO 88 TAXES/RESUME NBCC stuff USIS evaluation, 2006-ycal-2585-0033; 1 (Box 110)
    - MUSH ROAD TO HEAVEN UDUNIT DEATH OF BWAY FULL, 2006-ycal-2585-0034; 1 (Box 110)
    - BIBLIOG/XMAS CALENDAR MAILING etc TICKLER 90 TAXES D CONTENTS POETRY BOOKS POETRY FILES TAXES D XMASTRE CRD FULL, 2006-ycal-2585-0035; 1 (Box 110)
    - D.COM POEMS VOICES CONTENTS DAYONE, 2006-ycal-2585-0036; 1 (Box 110)
    - New POEMS '84 '85 D com, 2006-ycal-2585-0037; 1 (Box 110)
    - WORD STAR, 2006-ycal-2585-0038; 1 (Box 110)
    - DIARY 5 AUG 88 -- COPIED, 2006-ycal-2585-0039; 1 (Box 110)
    - LETTER #8 JAN '91-, 2006-ycal-2585-0040; 1 (Box 110)
    - LETTERS MAY89 #7 thru DEC '90 FULL, 2006-ycal-2585-0041; 1 (Box 110)
    - BOOK REVIEWS 4/90 FULL, 2006-ycal-2585-0042; 1 (Box 110)
    - Theatre 47+ thru 53 (Jan 90) (Oct '90) FULL, 2006-ycal-2585-0043; 1 (Box 111)
    - NEW GERMANY NEXT YEAR EGG + CHIPS JAHWEH'S WIFE INVISIBLE WOMAN, 2006-ycal-2585-0044; 1 (Box 111)
    - MUMMY'S B- CLUTE UDUNIT (Revision METAMOR2/DELANY SEQUELAE, 2006-ycal-2585-0045; 1 (Box 111)
    - KING OF THE K, 2006-ycal-2585-0046; 1 (Box 111)
    - ABDUCTED EIGHTFOLD MAY, 2006-ycal-2585-0047; 1 (Box 111)
    - ETERNITY RUSH LAKE MUSH ME OR US GHOST HAND D COM FULL, 2006-ycal-2585-0048; 1 (Box 111)
    - STRIEBER NATION-THEATER 1-4 FULL, 2006-ycal-2585-0049; 1 (Box 111)
    - THEATER 5+ through 12 FULL, 2006-ycal-2585-0050; 1 (Box 111)
    - Theatre 13+ FULL, 2006-ycal-2585-0051; 1 (Box 111)
    - THEATER 19+ --25 FULL, 2006-ycal-2585-0052; 1 (Box 111)
    - THEATER 26-32 plus Xmas 88, 2006-ycal-2585-0053; 1 (Box 111)
    - Theatre 33+ (Jan '89- Thru 39 (May '89 FULL, 2006-ycal-2585-0054; 1 (Box 111)
    - Theater 40+ (July '89) thru 46 (Jan 90) FULL, 2006-ycal-2585-0055; 1 (Box 111)
    - MIAMI VOICE MISSING HOURS FULL, 2006-ycal-2585-0056; 1 (Box 111)
    - SECOND COMING FULL, 2006-ycal-2585-0057; 1 (Box 111)
    - AUTOBIOG WILL 150K WILL, 2006-ycal-2585-0058; 1 (Box 111)
    - REVIEWS Oct-Dec 84 D.com, 2006-ycal-2585-0059; 1 (Box 111)
    - CELEBRITY LOVE BOOK REVS, 2006-ycal-2585-0060; 1 (Box 111)
    - A:/DEARVAL 2/19/05 A:\NEWTEST 2/22/95, 2006-ycal-2585-0061; 1 (Box 111)
    - STILL LIFE WITH FISH (Meta ?), 2006-ycal-2585-0062; 1 (Box 111)
    - Meta - revised May 2001, 2006-ycal-2585-0063; 1 (Box 111)
    - WP/stories, 2006-ycal-2585-0064; 1 (Box 111)
    - New Test 5/10/05, 2006-ycal-2585-0065; 1 (Box 111)
    - CHERVAG 1-7 6/10/01, 2006-ycal-2585-0066; 1 (Box 111)
    - Résumé, 2006-ycal-2585-0067; 1 (Box 111)
    - CHERVAG 1-7 11/04/00, 2006-ycal-2585-0068; 1 (Box 111)
    - metà complete (revised) backup, 2006-ycal-2585-0069; 1 (Box 111)
    - Tornado picture + crazy bunny game, 2006-ycal-2585-0070; 1 (Box 111)
    - [no label information], 2006-ycal-2585-0071; 1 (Box 111)
    - [no label information], 2006-ycal-2585-0072; 1 (Box 111)
    - [no label information], 2006-ycal-2585-0073; 1 (Box 111)
    - [no label information], 2006-ycal-2585-0074; 1 (Box 111)
    - KAYPRO WORKING DISKETTE THE WORD Plus, 2006-ycal-2585-0075; 1 (Box 111)
    - KAYPRO WORKING DISKETTE #2 PROFIT PLAN, 2006-ycal-2585-0076; 1 (Box 111)
    - KAYPRO WORKING DISKETTE WORDSTAR and MAILMERGE, 2006-ycal-2585-0077; 1 (Box 111)
    - KAYPRO WORKING DISKETTE DATASTAR, SUPERSORT, and CALCSTAR, 2006-ycal-2585-0078; 1 (Box 111)
    - SMARTKEY 5/6/84, 2006-ycal-2585-0079; 1 (Box 111)
    - KAYPRO WORKING DISKETTE Microsoft BASIC-80 PLUS SELECTED GAMES, 2006-ycal-2585-0080; 1 (Box 111)
    - KAYPRO WORKING DISKETTE CP/M Version 2.2, 2006-ycal-2585-0081; 1 (Box 111)
    - MDM 7 Modem software, 2006-ycal-2585-0082; 1 (Box 112)
    - Feature Format Gerrold Serial No. U0703O Format: KAYPRO, 2006-ycal-2585-0083; 1 (Box 112)
    - FF: AMN D, 2006-ycal-2585-0084; 1 (Box 112)
    - DIARY 1 OCT 84 FULL D PRINTED OUT COPIED, 2006-ycal-2585-0085; 1 (Box 112)
    - DIARY 2 MAY '85+ printed out, 2006-ycal-2585-0086; 1 (Box 112)
    - DIARY 3 - MAR1 '86 SEPT '86 printed out D.COM, 2006-ycal-2585-0087; 1 (Box 112)
    - DIARY 5 SEPT '88+, 2006-ycal-2585-0088; 1 (Box 112)
    - FULL PLAYBOY REVS TIMES RVS KRAZY KAT, 2006-ycal-2585-0089; 1 (Box 112)
    - REVIEWS '86 A. Mole Theroux McKenna Lite Verse NAND JEW POETS 88 AEGPT AM REN, 2006-ycal-2585-0090; 1 (Box 112)
    - REVIEWS '85 DeLillo - V. SETH FULL, 2006-ycal-2585-0091; 1 (Box 112)
    - LETTERS FULL D.COM, 2006-ycal-2585-0092; 1 (Box 112)
    - LETTERS 2 Feb '85-- Sept '85 FULL, 2006-ycal-2585-0093; 1 (Box 112)
    - LETTERS 4 Oct '86 + FULL, 2006-ycal-2585-0094; 1 (Box 112)
    - LETTERS 5 MARCH 88 + Jan 31 '89 FULL, 2006-ycal-2585-0095; 1 (Box 112)
    - DUTY + RESPONSE BACKUP, 2006-ycal-2585-0096; 1 (Box 112)
    - POEM OF DUTY, 2006-ycal-2585-0097; 1 (Box 112)
    - POEMS (copy) SUMMER '85 thru " '86 FULL, 2006-ycal-2585-0098; 1 (Box 112)
    - TLS - AMERICAN NOTES POST REVS. AM PART 1+2 DEFF CT, 2006-ycal-2585-0099; 1 (Box 112)
    - LETTERS 3 Sept '85-- FULL, 2006-ycal-2585-0100; 1 (Box 112)
    - Amnesia Side 3.5-A CMP3H10-5-84, 2006-ycal-2585-0101; 1 (Box 112)
    - IBM TEDDY BEAR By TOM DISCH, 2006-ycal-2585-0102; 1 (Box 112)
    - TEDDY, 2006-ycal-2585-0103; 1 (Box 112)
    - THE ANN NODE AMNESIA 6.1 4/4, 2006-ycal-2585-0104; 1 (Box 112)
  - "Museum," a diorama, undated (Box 114 (Art))